<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Solutions on Prilk IT consultancy</title><link>/solutions/</link><description>Recent content in Solutions on Prilk IT consultancy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/solutions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SAP CAR</title><link>/solutions/sap-car/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>/solutions/sap-car/</guid><description>Integrated SAP on Customer Activity Repository (CAR) System. SAP Customer Activity Repository (CAR) solutions helps businesses to enhance customer experience, accelerate decision making, improve demand planning, and maximize promotion effectiveness. This powerful data platform prepares cross-channel data by collating, cleansing, and centralizing your customer and point-of-sale (POS) data in real time for analysis and prepares it for consumption by other applications.
We have expertise on CAR solution and can propose solutions in maximizing the business benefits that you can achieve through CAR.</description></item><item><title>SAP Retail</title><link>/solutions/sap-retail/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate><guid>/solutions/sap-retail/</guid><description>Foreseeing shopper demand helps retailers deliver the right products to their stores and customers at the right time. Our expertise helps retailers streamline their entire supply chain system from planning to the fulfillment of orders. This helps retail enterprises gain transparency by efficiently tracking transit movement of goods and facilitating communication between warehouse management teams and logistic partners.
SAP Retail provides all the functions necessary for mapping your business processes in a retail company.</description></item><item><title>S/4 HANA</title><link>/solutions/s4-hana/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>/solutions/s4-hana/</guid><description>SAP, when fully utilized, simplifies business processes and enables enterprises to boost production, streamline operations, and function more economically. SAP technology implementations need to provide tangible business benefits as well as be scalable to changing business dynamics. Backed by our expertise SAP implementations and in-depth SAP knowledge, we provide SAP S/4HANA Implementation services that enable businesses to stay ahead of the demands, trends, and developments in the marketplace.
Why us for SAP S/4HANA Consulting Services?</description></item><item><title>SAP EWM</title><link>/solutions/sap-ewm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>/solutions/sap-ewm/</guid><description>Clients and system integrators alike utilize our SAP EWM services for supplementing teams and adding niche skill-sets as they take on additional projects. Our independent Subject Matter Experts (SMEs) have additional expertise in SAP WM, EDI, RF, and shipping integration platforms. We provide consultants for roles such as SAP EWM Functional and Technical Consultants, SAP ABAP Technical Leads and Programmers, SAP QA, SAP BA and BI, and SAP EWM/WM Trainers. With our approach, you receive an experienced team that you own and control for as long as it takes to implement your solution, ensuring better control over deliverables.</description></item></channel></rss>